<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blakerspace</title><link>https://blakerspace.net/</link><description>Recent content on Blakerspace</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +1100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blakerspace.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>I learnt to code on World of Warcraft private servers</title><link>https://blakerspace.net/blog/private-server-history/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +1100</pubDate><guid>https://blakerspace.net/blog/private-server-history/</guid><description>When I was 13 years old I wanted to play World of Warcraft, but my parents wouldn&amp;rsquo;t let me buy a subscription.
Because of that, today, I write software for a living.
Pretty much my entire high school life, after school, was spent on the computer, fixing a bootleg free version of World of Warcraft.</description></item><item><title>My Management Academy, Episode 1</title><link>https://blakerspace.net/blog/my-management-academy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://blakerspace.net/blog/my-management-academy/</guid><description>What is this? A timeline of my move from software developer to engineering manager, with structured advice along the way Anime themed, for no good reason. Who is this for? A software developer considering management Someone currently on the path to becoming a leader Anyone curious about the transition from individual contributor to management. Welcome to My Management Academy &amp;lt;anime noises&amp;gt; Hi, the name’s Blake Miyazaki, but you can just call me Blake.</description></item><item><title>Where am I?</title><link>https://blakerspace.net/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blakerspace.net/about/</guid><description>You&amp;rsquo;re here.
The Blakerspace.
What happens when the web meets weeb? When Medium and LinkedIn are too pretentious, but this is somehow acceptable? When professional and personal are inextricably linked like an overshare at the christmas party?
Where songs you discover are anime openings and so you watch the anime and it&amp;rsquo;s also good.
A place in Sydney that serves The Premium Malt&amp;rsquo;s.
Where the decisions matter so little that any</description></item></channel></rss>