<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Ramblings on Blakerspace</title><link>https://blakerspace.net/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Ramblings on Blakerspace</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blakerspace.net/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Going infinite on Boost bars</title><link>https://blakerspace.net/blog/boost-bars/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blakerspace.net/blog/boost-bars/</guid><description>A sweet treat If you know me, you know I love a sweet treat after a main meal. I had just finished my lunch at work and that all too familiar need for a sweet treat visited. I head down to the nearby Woolworths Metro, and hunt through its labyrinthine aisles hunting for the right treat.
The choccies caught my eye. Cadbury were running a promotion where buying any specially marked bar gave you the chance to win a second free bar.</description></item><item><title>I learnt to code on World of Warcraft private servers</title><link>https://blakerspace.net/blog/private-server-history/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blakerspace.net/blog/private-server-history/</guid><description>When I was 13 years old I wanted to play World of Warcraft, but my parents wouldn&amp;rsquo;t let me buy a subscription.
Because of that, today, I write software for a living.
Pretty much my entire high school life, after school, was spent on the computer, fixing a bootleg free version of World of Warcraft. This is how I learnt to code! I&amp;rsquo;ve told some close friends bits and pieces of this story and it has been met with demand for more detail, so I&amp;rsquo;m taking that as an excuse to write it all down.</description></item><item><title>My Management Academy, Episode 1</title><link>https://blakerspace.net/blog/my-management-academy/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://blakerspace.net/blog/my-management-academy/</guid><description>What is this? A timeline of my move from software developer to engineering manager, with structured advice along the way Anime themed, for no good reason. Who is this for? A software developer considering management Someone currently on the path to becoming a leader Anyone curious about the transition from individual contributor to management. Welcome to My Management Academy &amp;lt;anime noises&amp;gt; Hi, the name’s Blake Miyazaki, but you can just call me Blake.</description></item></channel></rss>